<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Konkani Culture</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Konkani Culture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Literature</title>
      <link>/literature/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/literature/</guid>
      <description> News articles: 2017  Konkani: a language in crisis livemint.com Konkani vs. Marathi language battles in Goa livemint.com Oh Konkani, my sweet mother tongue thequint.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Structure</title>
      <link>/project-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project-structure/</guid>
      <description>Last Updated: Sep 11th 2017
With the advent of cloud machine learning systems, it is proposed to use these technologies to assist and speed up the work associated with the main goals.
 Optical Character Recognition (OCR) of any Konkani dialect script (Kannada, Roman, Marathi) text into its Unicode text form. Translate any Konkani dialect in Unicode Form into English and vice-versa. (requires grammar analysis) Create a audio reader for text in any dialect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Post for Blogdown</title>
      <link>/post/test-post-for-blogdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/test-post-for-blogdown/</guid>
      <description>Here we are tyring to publish some things about R.
R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Nov 14th 2016: To create a detailed and comprehensive record of the Konkani culture and preserve it digitally and in archives in institutions all over the world. The situation:
This is the beginning of the end.
 Lack of motivation among parents to teach their children the Konkani language and history has lead to a stage where there are not enough people to take Konkani culture to the next generation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>